瑞秋 松饼加浓缩咖啡4块5
Okay, Rach, that's muffin and espresso, 4.50.
罗斯 双份拿铁2块75 钱德 咖啡和司康4块25
Ross, double latte, 2.75. Chandler, coffee and a scone, 4.25.
菲比 花茶1块25
And, Pheebs, herbal tea, 1.25.
总共是...12块75
So all together that's 12.75.
这是80元电话费除以二 不会除的人
This coming from the man who couldn't split our $80 phone bill in half.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
我的松饼和拿铁多少钱？
How much do I owe?
你的由乔伊崔比亚尼免费招持
Oh, that's on the house, courtesy of Joey Tribbiani.
真好 帮我谢谢他
Oh. Great. Well, tell him thanks.
既然乔伊人这么好 也许我们可以约个会
And since Joey seems like such a nice guy, maybe we could go on a date sometime?
他不太习惯女人这么主动
Well, he's not used to women being so forward...
不过我问过他 他说好
but I could check with him. He says it's okay.
太好了 谢谢 再见
Great. Thanks. Bye-bye.
乔伊 为什么我们不是免费？
Hey, Joey, how come our stuff isn't free?
等你穿窄裙也那么辣就有了
It will be when you look like that in a tight skirt.
真好 我的约会破纪录的多
This is great. I'm getting more dates than ever.
慢着 你只算美女免费？
Wait, you're only giving away free stuff to the pretty girls?
对啊 好恶心喔
Joey, that is so gross.
要不要来一块免费司康？
Hmm. How about a scone on the house, baby?
我是美女
I'm pretty.
老友记 第六季 第十三集
- 有人有口香糖吗？ - 我有
- Hey, does anyone have any gum?     - Oh, I do.
拿一下
Here. Sorry.
好像是...
Oh, you know what?
不是
No.
等一下
Wait a second.
- 我记得我有   - 算了 不用了
- I know it's in here somewhere.     - You know what? I'm good. I'm good.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你怎么回来了？不是在上班？
What are you doing here? Shouldn't you be at work?
他们叫我回家 说什么感冒不能做菜
They sent me home. They said I can't work if I'm sick.
- 噢 真可怜   - 我没有感冒
- Aw. I'm so sorry that you're sick.     - I'm not sick.
我才不会感冒
I don't get sick.
软弱和娘娘腔的人才会感冒
Getting sick is for weaklings. It's for pansies.
没有人觉得你娘娘腔
Honey, no one thinks that you're a pansy.
但我们觉得你需要面纸
But we do think that you need a tissue.
我已经3年多没感冒了
I have not been sick in over three years.
- 我帮你拿几张面纸   - 我不需要面纸 我很好...哪
- I'm gonna grab you some tissue.     - I don't need a tissue. I'm fine.
好的后面还加个哪 就不好哪
When you put a D at the end of "fine," you're not fine.
我很好...哪
I'm fine.
这句话很难说
You know, it's a really hard word to say.
- 哪位？ - 瑞秋在吗？我是她的妹妹
- Yes?     - Hi. Is Rachel here? I'm her sister.
- 天哪 吉儿   - 天哪 瑞秋
- Oh, my God, Jill.     - Oh, my God, Rachel.
天哪 介绍一下吧
Oh, my God, introduce us.
- 这位是钱德   - 你好
- This is Chandler.     - Hi.
你认识摩妮卡和罗斯
And you know Monica and Ross.
- 嗨   - 那是菲比 那是乔伊
- Hi.     - And that's Phoebe, and that's Joey.
- 你好吗？ - 不好
- Hey. How you doing?     - Don't.
- 你怎么来了？ - 噢
- Honey, what are you doing here?     - Oh.
这是哪个妹妹？
Which sister is this?
被宠坏的还是咬她的那一位？
Is this the spoiled one or the one that bit her?
- 老爸断了我的财源   - 我知道了
- Daddy cut me off.     - Never mind, I got it.
你知道我怎么说？
And you know what I said to him?
我说"我要请一个律师 把你的钱都告过来
I said, "I'm gonna hire a lawyer, sue you and take all your money...
然后断了你的财源"
and then I'm gonna cut you off."
- 那他怎么说？ - 他说不帮我付律师费
- What did he say?     - He said he wouldn't pay for my lawyer.
- 啊   - 还叫我来跟他唯一自豪的女儿
- Ah.     - Then he told me to come and learn the value of money...
- 学学金钱的价值   - 哦
- from the one daughter he's proud of.   - Oh.
你们听到了吗？我爸以我为荣 我爸以我为荣
Did you hear that? My dad's proud of me. My dad's proud of me. Ha, ha.
- 瑞秋？ - 好 抱歉
- Rach?     - Oh, yeah, sorry.
爸为什么不给你钱？
Hey, honey, so, what did you do that made Dad cut you off?
- 我买了艘船   - 你买了艘船？
- Okay, I bought a boat.     - You bought a boat?
不是我要的 是要送朋友的
Yeah, but it wasn't for me, it was for a friend.
我们不该跟姊姊交朋友的
Boy, did we make friends with the wrong sister.
吉儿 这是一次最好的教训
Jill, I think this is the best thing that could've ever happened to you.
反正你也得独立
You've needed to get out on your own anyway.
我刚独立时也很害怕
And you know, when I did it, at first I was scared...
结果现在呢
but then look at me now.
我是唯一让老爸骄傲的女儿
I am the only daughter that Dad is proud of.
你现在要做的是找一份工作
Okay, well, this is what you're gonna do. You're gonna get a job.
找一间公寓 我会帮你
You're gonna get an apartment. And I'll help you.
你可以跟我们住 对吧？菲比 可以吧？
You can stay with us. Right? She can stay with us?
- 当然可以   - 太好了
- Of course, yeah.     - Oh, that's so great.
好 那我就来独立 真不知道该怎么谢谢你们
Okay, I'm really gonna do this. I don't know how to thank you guys.
我喜欢汽车
Aw. I like cars.
（中央咖啡厅）
- 你还要用吗？ - 不要了
- You all finished here?     - Yes.
太好了
Great.
- 早上的小费出来了   - 嗯
- Okay, here are the tips for this morning.     - Mm.
珍50、我50 乔伊欠8块钱
Jen gets 50, 50 for me, and Joey owes $8.
- 什么？ - 因为你到处送吃的
- What?     - For all the free food you gave away.
既然是送的 为什么跟我要钱
Well, if it's free food, how come you're charging me for it?
我们只免费招持寿星
We don't give anything away unless it's someone's birthday.
那模特儿比赛第三名呢？
Oh. What if they came in third in a modeling contest?
- 不行   - 抱歉
- No.     - Oh. Sorry.
我今天好惨 这些袋子好重
I just had the hardest day. Some of these are so heavy.
吉儿 你怎么有钱？你爸不是把信用卡都收走了？
Jill, how did you pay for all this? I thought your dad took your credit card.
拜托 我15岁就会背卡号了
Oh, please, I memorized those numbers when I was 15.
你们看我买的这些独立行头
But look at all the cool make-it-on-my-own stuff I got.
这是"请雇用我"毛衣
This is my "Please hire me" sweater.
这是"你不想把房子租我吗"裤子
And these are my "Don't you want to rent me this apartment?" pants.
叫你爸付你的置装费不算独立
I don't think charging clothes to your dad qualifies as making it on your own.
大科学家就是这么死板
Oh, Mr. Scientist has to get all technical.
瑞秋真的不会赞成
I don't think Rachel's gonna think it's a good idea.
- 谁封她当女王了？ - 我超想当女王的
- So who made her queen of the world?     - I would love that job.
- 怎么样啊？ - 嘿
- Hey. What's going on?     - Hey.
吉儿
Jill.
你跑去逛街吗？
Did you shop?
没有
No.
是他们
They did.
- 对 我们跑去进街   - 对 我们跑去逛街
- Yeah, we went shopping.     - Yeah, we went shopping. Yeah.
你们跑去进街？
You went shopping?
然后把东西秀给吉儿看？
Then you came in here and paraded it right under Jill's nose...
你们明知她想戒掉
when you know she's trying to quit.
你们真差劲
Wow. You guys, that's terrible.
- 抱歉 吉儿   - 吉儿 对不起
- Sorry, Jill.     - Sorry, Jill.
没关系
It's okay.
- 你们买了什么？ - 我买了...谢谢
- So, what did you get?     - Oh, well, all right. I got... Thank you.
- 我买了这件 "我要工作"毛衣   - 噢
- I got, um, this, you know, "I want a job" sweater.     - Oh.
还买了这条公寓裤
And then I got, uh... These are apartment pants.
公寓裤？
Apartment pants?
对 你没听过吗？
Yeah, you've never heard of them?
当然听过
No, of course. Of course I've heard of them.
- 罗斯那你呢？ - 嗯？
- Ross, what did you get?     - Huh?
我买了这个...
I got this...
这个
This.
- 喀什米尔？ - 对
- A pashmina?     - Yeah.
我爱死它了
Oh, I love these babies.
- 是吗？ - 嗯
- Really?     - Mm-hm.
罗斯 喀什米尔是什么？
Ross, what's a pashmina?
一种小毯子
It's a rug.
吉儿？
Jill?
瑞秋 对不起...
I'm sorry, Rachel.
拜托 你真以为我会上当？
Oh, come on, you really think that's gonna work on me?
泪眼攻势是我发明的
I invented that.
也对 但我真的很抱歉
Oh, right. But I am sorry.
算了 走一次回头路还好
All right, it's okay. One little setback is okay.
- 就是别再犯了 好吗？ - 好
- But don't let it happen again, all right?     - Okay.
既然这是老爸付的钱 我应该全都没收
Now, since Daddy paid for all this stuff, I should take it all away.
不过我没收披肩就好
But I'm just gonna take the pashmina.
还有那条裤子
And the pants.
还是都没收好了 这样你才能得到教训
You know what? I'm just gonna take it all, because that way, you'll learn the lesson.
好了
Alrighty.
我有事要忙 我们晚餐见
I'm gonna run a couple of errands, and I will see you at dinner.
都被她拿走了
She took all my stuff.
没错 除了这个蓝色小袋子
Yeah. Everything but the little blue one.
这一样最棒了
That's the best one.
- 天哪 谢谢你   - 这个嘛
- Oh, my God. Thank you so much.     - Oh. Well, hey.
天哪 你好逊喔 喀什米尔怎么会是小毯子
Oh, my gosh, that was so lame. Like a pashmina could be a rug.
那你呢？
Oh, yeah? Well, how about you with the:
- "对不起..."   - 闭嘴 我哪有那么恶心
- "I'm sorry."     - Shut up. I wasn't like that at all.
我那个公寓裤呢？
What about what I said, you know, about the apartment pants?
够蠢吧？
How dumb was I?
- 你高中时有这么可爱吗？ - 别闹了
- Were you this cute in high school?     - Oh, stop.
- 你才别闹了   - 你才别闹了
- No, you stop.     - No, you stop.
你别闹了
You stop.
好 我坐中间 你们都别闹了
Okay, why don't I sit here and then you'll both stop it?
你想做什么？我们来疯一下
Okay, so, what do you wanna do? Let's do something crazy.
我知道 我们来多休息多喝水
I know, let's rest and drink lots of fluids.
好 我休息
Okay, I'll rest.
不过如果我要上床 你也得跟我来
But, you know, if I'm going to bed, then you're coming with me.
我本来很难说不 但是你鼻水流不停
See, that would be impossible to resist if you weren't all drippy here.
你是说你不想要我吗？
Are you saying that you don't wanna get with this?
你最好连健康时都不要这样
Yeah, I don't think you should say that even when you're healthy.
来嘛
Oh. Come on.
我不是针对你
Don't take this personally, okay?
我就是没办法跟病人上床
It's just that I just can't have sex with a sick person.
我也是
I'm with you, Chandler.
我也不跟病人上床 那样好恶心
I can't have sex with a sick person either. That's disgusting.
但是我没病 让我证明给你看
But I'm not sick. Let me prove it to you.
我们身强体壮 青春正盛
We are two healthy people in the prime of life.
我就是想继续身强体壮
See, that's the thing. I would like to stay in the prime of life.
嘿
Hey.
- 嘿   - 怎么样啊？
- Hey.     - What's up?
有件事或许你应该知道
Um, I think there's something you should maybe know.
最好不是公寓裤的事
It better not be about the apartment pants...
因为我的上司爱死这个构想了
because I just pitched the idea to my boss at Ralph Lauren, and she loved it.
不是 我刚...
No, no. It's just, I was, um...
你走了后 我跟罗斯和吉儿在一起
I was with Ross and Jill after you left...
我很确定他们之间有火花
and I'm pretty sure I saw a little spark between them.
- 什么？ - 或许没事
- What?     - Yeah, I mean, it's probably nothing.
我只是想提醒你 他们或许有什么
But I just wanted to warn you that there might be something there.
- 罗斯跟吉儿？ - 对
- With Ross and Jill?     - Yeah.
罗斯和我妹妹？
With Ross and my sister?
- 是啊   - 我妹吉儿和我的前男友罗斯？
- Yeah.     - With my sister Jill and my ex-boyfriend Ross?
- 是啊   - 不可能的   - 那好吧
- Yeah.     - Oh, there is no way.     - Okay, then.
我的天哪 我真不敢相信
Oh, my God. I cannot believe that.
不是我反对罗斯交女朋友 但居然跟我妹
I don't really like it when Ross goes out with anyone, but my sister?
这不是等于乱伦吗？
Isn't that like incest or something?
天哪 而且他们会上床 要是他还娶她呢？
Oh, my God, and they're gonna have sex. Oh, no. What if he marries her too?
太恐怖了 真是太恐怖了
Oh, this is just terrible. This is just terrible.
而我又不能阻止 罗斯又不是我的
And I can't stop it. I don't own Ross, you know?
而且吉儿有她的行动自由
And Jill, she should be able to do whatever it is she wants to do.
我的天哪 罗斯居然要娶我妹
Oh, my God, I can't believe Ross is marrying my little sister.
这简直...
This is just...
天那 这真是我这一生最悲惨的遭遇
Oh, my God, this is just the worst thing that could've ever happened to me.
不过公寓裤的事真是太好了
But great news about the apartment pants, huh?
总共3块85
That'll be 3.85.
什么意思？昨天你还说我太美不该付钱
What do you mean? Yesterday you said I was too pretty to pay.
我不能请客 因为经理说我...
It's just I can't, because my manager said that I...
祝你生日快乐 祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you.
- 祝安妮生日快乐   - 艾美
- Happy birthday, dear Annie...     - Amy.
艾美
Amy
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
- 嘿   - 还真巧 今天也是我的生日
- Hey.     - Hey, that's weird, today's my birthday too.
在这里不是
Yeah, not in here it isn't.
抱歉迟到了 什么事？
Sorry I'm late. What's up?
哦 嘿
Oh, hey. Uh...
我只是想问你工作找得怎样
You know, I just wanted to see if there were any leads on the old job front.
没进展 但我经过三家折和店都没进去
Oh. No. But I just walked past three sales and I didn't go in.
- 我很坚强吧？ - 哦
- How strong am I?     - Oh.
太好了
That is great.
你知道谁不必找工作？
Hey, you know who doesn't have to job-hunt?
- 罗斯 他在大学教书   - 是啊
- Ross. He works at the university.     - Yeah?
所以你知道 你们聊过 你们很投缘 你们要约会吗？
Oh, so you know that? You guys talked? So you get along? So you're gonna go out?
我跟罗斯约会？当然不会 你哪来的念头？
Me go out with Ross? No. God, no. What would make you think that?
就...菲比...
It's just Phoebe...
觉得你们有什么
said she, you know, thought she saw something between you guys.
- 没有 他人是很好   - 是啊
- No. I mean, he's nice.     - Yeah.
你会想和他做朋友 但不会想和他交往
He's the kind of guy you're friends with but not the kind of guy you date.
你会 你跟他交往过 我呢？
I mean, he's the kind of guy you date, because you did, but me?
就没什么兴趣
Hmm, not so much.
没什么兴趣？什么意思？
Oh, not so much? What do you mean?
罗斯有哪里不好吗？
I mean, is there something wrong with Ross?
没有 只不过...
Oh, no, no, no. He's just...
我不知道...他有点书呆吧
I don't know. You know, he's just a little bookish.
- 你觉得他是怪胎？ - 你也有同感？
- Are you saying he's a geek?     - You think so too?
不 罗斯不是怪胎
No. No. Ross is not a geek.
好 就当他不是我喜欢的型
Fine. Then let's just say he's not my type.
你不喜欢帅哥？
What, handsome is not your type?
聪明？好心？吻功一流？这些不是你的条件？
Smart, kind, good kisser? What, those things aren't on your list?
罗斯人很好 能跟他在一起是你的福气
Ross is a great guy. You would be lucky to be with him.
好 既然你这么在意 我就约他
Well, okay, if it means that much to you, I'll ask him out.
不不不 我不是那个意思
Oh, no, no, no. That's not what I meant. I was just...
你知道吗？你说得对 他对我确实很好
You know what, Rachel? You're right. You know, he has been really nice to me.
但他不是你的型
Yeah, but he's not your type.
或许这是好事
But maybe that's a good thing.
我正在做各种尝试
You know, I'm doing all these different things.
或许也应该跟怪胎约会看看
Maybe I should just try dating a geek too.
但你也别一下子做太多尝试
Yeah, but you don't, you know... You don't wanna try too much too fast.
你记得那个一下子做太多尝试的...
I mean, you do remember what happened to the little girl...
小女孩吧
who tried too much too fast, don't you?
什么？
What?
她死了
She died, Jill.
钱德
Chandler.
什么事 你想喝茶？还是喝汤？
What is it, honey? You need some tea? Some soup?
哦 哦
Oh. Oh.
呼叫大鹏医生 大鹏医生请上床
Calling Dr. Big. Dr. Big to the bed.
天哪 我以为你睡了
Oh, jeez, honey, I thought you were asleep.
你就在外面 我怎么睡得着？
How could I be asleep knowing that you were in the next room?
我倒是睡着了
I was asleep.
不 你知道怎样才性感？多穿几层
Oh, no, no, no, honey. You know what's sexy? Layers.
多穿几层才性感
Layers are sexy.
被子才性感 热水袋更性感
And blankets are sexy. And, oh, hot water bottles are sexy.
上床啦 我想证明我没生病
Come on, get into bed. I wanna prove that I'm not sick.
我想让你跟我一样舒服
I wanna make you feel as good as I feel.
- 我拜托你休息   - 我没事哪
- Would you please get some rest?     - I'm fine.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
- 你出钱   - 不 今天是她的生日
- You're paying for that.     - What? No, no, it's her birthday.
你已经对廿个女人唱生日快乐
You've sung "Happy Birthday" to 20 different women today.
- 但是...   - 你失去送...
- But it...     - You are no longer authorized...
生日松饼的权限了
to distribute birthday muffins.
妈的
Damn it.
瑞秋
Rach.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi. Ahem.
你叫你妹约我吗？
Did you tell your sister to ask me out?
- 对...   - 哇 真是 哇
- Well, yeah.     - Oh, wow. I mean, wow.
我觉得她很可爱
I think she's cute...
但我从来没想过要跟她约会
but I never would've thought of going out with her. Never.
- 真的？ - 对啊
- Really?     - Yeah.
不过既然你说行 我心想:有何不可？
But after you said it was okay, I figured, why not?
所以也不算从来没想过
Oh, so not really "never." Heh.
你真的比我大方多了
I have to say, you are a much bigger person than I am.
我们有那么多过去 我...
I mean, after all we've been through. I just...
真希望我有兄弟可以做交换
You know what? I wish I had a brother to reciprocate.
啊哦
Aw.
如果你想跟摩妮卡交往 我绝对祝福
Hey, if you ever wanna go out with Monica, you have my blessing.
我也是
And mine.
钱德
Chandler?
我觉得我病了
I think I'm sick.
是吗？
Really?
青春不盛了
Struck down in the prime of life.
好啦 我承认 我很不舒服
Okay, fine, I admit it. I feel terrible.
- 帮我在胸口抹药膏   - 好
- Will you please rub this on my chest?     - Okay.
不行 你别想骗我上钩
No, no, no. You are not getting me this way.
- 我真的需要你帮我...   - 不行
- Come on, I really need your help here.     - No, no, no.
- 好 那我就自己抹   - 好
- Fine, I'll rub it on myself.     - Okay.
你在往身上抹药膏？
So you're just kind of rubbing it on yourself?
- 怎样？ - 蛮好的
- Yeah.     - It's nice.
不会吧？这样你会兴奋？
Are you kidding me? Is this turning you on?
对
Yes.
真是太扯了 是抹的动作还是味道？
I can't believe it. Is it the rubbing or the smell?
都很赞
It's all very, very good.
想不想...
So you wanna go, uh...
嘿咻一下？
mix it up?
- 现在不行 我病了   - 少来了 大骗子
- Not now, I'm sick.     - Oh, come on, you big faker.
你不是不跟病人上床？
What about your rule about never sleeping with sick people?
那是在那令人酥麻的动作之前
Well, that was before all the vaporizing action.
- 好吧 如果你真的想做...   - 好
- Okay, if you really wanna have sex.     - Okay.
有够灵的
Worked like a charm.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
你来这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
我跟罗斯约在这里 我的打扮如何？
This is where Ross and I are meeting for our date. So, what do you think?
我不喜欢
I don't like it.
- 是吗？ - 有点下贱
- Really?     - It's kind of slutty.
这是你的衣服
It's yours.
我是个贱人
Yeah, well, I'm a slut.
我也是
Me too.
- 嗨 吉儿   - 嘿
- Hi, Jill.     - Hey.
嗨...
Hi...
- 瑞秋   - 瑞秋
- Rachel.     - Rachel.
你不在家 你在这里
Heh. You're not at home, you're right here.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
你一定以为会很怪 其实不会
And I bet you thought it would be weird. But it's not.
那么...
So, well, I'll, um...
我午夜之前会送她回家
I'll have her home by midnight. Ha, ha.
你为什么还没回家
Why aren't you home yet?
外面有人吗？
Is someone there?
有 是我 抱歉
Oh, yeah, it's me. Sorry.
你来干什么？
What are you doing here?
我只是在看窗外...的风景
Uh, I'm just looking out your window at the view.
你们在干什么？
What are you guys doing?
我们身上沾到药膏
We got some VapoRub in some places.
他把她带回家了
Oh. He brought her back to his apartment.
谁？
Who?
那是你妹妹吗？
Is that your sister?
她真是个贱人
Ugh. She is a slut.
罗斯在跟你妹约会 多奇怪啊
God. Ross is on a date with your sister. How weird is that?
天哪 看 他在脱她的衣服
Oh, my God, look, he's taking off her clothes.
他在帮她脱外套
He's taking off her coat.
真是太糟糕了
Oh, this is just terrible.
不会啦 才第一次约会 一定不会有...
Oh, no, it's not. It was the first date. I'm sure that nothing is gonna...
他有福了...
Hoo-hoo. He's gonna get some.
能看到屋外...
Of the glare...
街灯的灯光
from the streetlight out of his apartment.
所以他把窗帘拉上
You know, so, um, he's closed the drapes there...
好跟你妹好好聊一聊
so he can have a nice pleasant conversation with your little sister.
我去睡了
Well, I'm off to bed.
（未完待续）